# **Drishti Bahl**

Cybersecurity Undergraduate



### Personal details



Drishti Bahl



drishtibahl68@gmail.com



(+91) 8800401109



drishtibahl12.github.io/MyPortfoli



linkedin.com/in/drishti-bahl-37a487196



github.com/drishtibahl12

### Skills

Kali Linux	••••
Nmap	••••
Python	••••
HTML & CSS3	••••
Nessus Tool	••••
Basic Networking	••••
Team Player	••••
Work Ethics	••••

## Certificates

- CEH v11 by EC-Council
- Security+ by CompTIA (On-Going)
- Cyberops Associate by C.N.A.
- Hack NU 3.0 by NIIT University

### **Profile**

A passionate Computer Science student. Cybersecurity and networking are at the forefront of my research and career interests. Enthusiastic and dedicated to my work. As a member of the team, I will use my public relations and problem-solving skills along with my core cybersecurity skills, to add more value to the firm.

## Work Experience

### **Cybersecurity Analyst Intern**

Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

**Craw Security** 

- Brushed and implemented the knowledge of tools like **Nmap**, **Metasploit**, etc.
- Collaborated with different teams and learnt a lot about the work environment.

#### **Interned at Cisco**

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021

Cisco Virtual Internship Program

• Learnt basics of networking and applied using Packet Tracer to build the network of an organization.

# **Projects**

### **Password cracking**

• In this project, I cracked the password using the basics of Python Language.

#### (R&D) - Impact of Video Knowledge base

• Implemented Video Knowledge Base in NIIT University.

#### C.R.U.D. Application

• Implemented create, retrieve, update and delete in a simple application.

### Evolution from 5G to 6G - Research

• Purely research based project about 6G Technology .

### Education

### B.Tech. in C.S.E.

Aug 2019 - Present

NIIT University, Neemrana Specialisation: Cybersecurity Aggregated C.G.P.A.: 7.31

#### **Senior Secondary Grade XII**

Apr 2018 - Mar 2019

Ahlcon Public School, Noida

The Khaitan School, Noida

Science, P.C.M. Board: C.B.S.E. Percentage: 94.8%

### **Schooling Grade X**

Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

Board: C.B.S.E.

C.G.P.A.: 9.8

# Positions of Responsibility

- SPOC at TedXNIITUniversity (Nov 2019 Feb 2020)
- Mentor in NanoEPL, NIIT University (Sept 2020 Dec 2020)
- Public Relations Head at Annual Tech-Fest (Jan 2021 Dec 2021)